priceofweb.com 2016-04-08

# TheDomainValue Terms and conditions

##### Privacy Policy

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal (if any) and domain related information..

##### 1\. What information do we collect? 

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of data related to the domain only:  
(a) Information provided by Alexa.com related to your domain   
(b) Information provided by Google.com like Google Page rank, Google Page Speed related to your domain only.   
(c) Other information of your domain like DNS records, website Meta data, website ip address, website title and description (if found any) fetched from website header request .  
(d) Information like Social analysis, website thumbnail, website favicon, location of server (where website is hosted) etc. are collected from various Api (third party) and we are just showing them to our website.  
(e) Few data like websie worth, website estimated price, estimated ad revenue, estimated page views, bandwidth , monthly revenue of the site are being created programmatically based on the data we have collected via different api (third party).   

##### 2\. Information about website visits 

Third party api may collect information about your computer and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views. These information can be used, to improve the website's usability, and for marketing purposes.

#####  3\. Using your personal data

Personal data (if any) submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.  
In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may use your personal information to:  
(a) Improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website;  
(b) To contact you about features and updates about exclusively.  
(c) Using your domain data like domain registration date can be used to create domain age.

#####  4\. Other disclosures

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about your domain:  
(a) To the extent that we are required to do so by law;  
(b) In connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;  
(c) In order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk); and  
(d) To the purchaser or seller (or prospective purchaser or seller) of any business or asset which we are (or are contemplating) selling or purchasing.  
We may also provide few information of your domain to the third parties to collect more information so that you can understand the your domain analytics in more effective way.   

#####  5\. Security of your personal data

We will take reasonable precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information (if any). Of course, data transmission over the internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the internet.

#####  6\. Policy amendments 

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

##### 7\. Your rights

You may instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. As of now we are not storing any personal data of any domain webmaster. We are not even storing the personal data showing with website WHOIS.

##### 8\. Third party websites

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the content, terms and conditions or privacy policies of third party websites.

##### 9.Cookies/Cache

This site uses cache to serve the page with minimum downloading and optimized files so that same file should not take your bandwidth again. We are not storing any Cookies but cookie can be store by any third parties used in the site to server better performance. 

##### 10\. Contact

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to [thedomainvalue@gmail.com](mailto:thedomainvalue@gmail.com?Subject=Contact%20from%20Site%20Privacy).
